<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<GenAiPlugin xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <canEscalate>false</canEscalate>
    <description>Manages provider network roster file ingestion. Handles any request to validate, stage, map fields for, or ingest a provider roster CSV file attached to a Case Related File record. Also handles requests to check ingestion status or view ingestion results.</description>
    <developerName>ProviderRosterManagement</developerName>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>EmployeeCopilot__GetRecordDetails</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>ValidateRosterFile</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>StageRosterFile</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>ManageRosterFieldMapping</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>TriggerRosterIngestion</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>When the user asks to process, validate, stage, or ingest a roster file: call GetRecordDetails with the CRF record ID the user provides (e.g. CRF-000000001 or 1FxIf000000blRZKAY) to retrieve the CRF record. The object type is CaseRelatedFile. From the result, read ProcessStage and ProcessStatus to determine the workflow step, and confirm the record exists before proceeding.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_get_context0</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_get_context0</masterLabel>
        <sortOrder>0</sortOrder>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>After GetRecordDetails returns the CRF record, determine the next step from ProcessStage and ProcessStatus: if both are blank or null = FRESH (validate then stage); if ProcessStage = Staging and ProcessStatus = Complete = STAGED (go to mapping); if ProcessStage = Mapping and ProcessStatus = InReview = ask admin to set status to Completed; if ProcessStage = Mapping and ProcessStatus = Complete = trigger ingestion; if ProcessStage = Processing and ProcessStatus = InProgress = tell admin job is running.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_routing1</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_routing1</masterLabel>
        <sortOrder>1</sortOrder>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>For FRESH state: call ValidateRosterFile passing the CRF record Id from GetRecordDetails as crfId. The action reads the attached CSV file automatically — never ask the user for file contents. Narrate validation results. Pass the validatedRowsJson output directly to StageRosterFile along with the same crfId. Always confirm with the admin before staging, mapping, or ingesting.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_validate_stage2</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_validate_stage2</masterLabel>
        <sortOrder>2</sortOrder>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>After DPE mapping is triggered via ManageRosterFieldMapping in TRIGGER mode, give the admin a link to the CRF record to complete the mapping review. Poll in POLL mode until mappingComplete = true. Do not trigger ingestion until then. When ingestion is triggered via TriggerRosterIngestion, tell the admin they can close the chat and will be notified when the job finishes. Do not mention time estimates.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_mapping_ingest3</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_mapping_ingest3</masterLabel>
        <sortOrder>3</sortOrder>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <masterLabel>Provider Roster Management</masterLabel>
    <pluginType>Topic</pluginType>
    <scope>Handle all requests related to provider roster file ingestion: processing a roster file, validating, staging, field mapping, running ingestion, and checking ingestion status or results. Triggered when the user mentions a roster file, a CRF record, or provider network data loading. The roster file is already attached to the CRF record in Salesforce — no file transfer from the user is needed.</scope>
</GenAiPlugin>
