<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<GenAiPlugin xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <canEscalate>false</canEscalate>
    <description>Manages provider network roster file ingestion. Handles any request to validate, stage, map fields for, or ingest a provider roster CSV file attached to a Case Related File record. Also handles requests to check ingestion status or view ingestion results.</description>
    <developerName>ProviderRosterManagement</developerName>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>GetRosterCRFContext</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>ValidateRosterFile</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>StageRosterFile</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>ManageRosterFieldMapping</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiFunctions>
        <functionName>TriggerRosterIngestion</functionName>
    </genAiFunctions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>When the user asks to process, validate, stage, or ingest a roster file: call GetRosterCRFContext with the CRF record ID from page context. If no currentRecordId is available, ask the user to provide the CRF record ID. The file is already attached to the CRF record — you do not need to receive or transfer any file from the user.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_start0</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_start0</masterLabel>
        <sortOrder>0</sortOrder>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>After GetRosterCRFContext returns, use agentResumeInstruction to decide next step. FRESH: call ValidateRosterFile with the crfId, then StageRosterFile. STAGED: go to DPE mapping. MAPPING_IN_REVIEW: ask admin to set CRF mapping status to Completed. MAPPING_COMPLETE: offer to trigger ingestion. INGESTION_RUNNING: tell admin the job is running. INGESTION_COMPLETE: show summary.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_routing1</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_routing1</masterLabel>
        <sortOrder>1</sortOrder>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>To validate: call ValidateRosterFile with the crfId. The action reads the file from the CRF record automatically — you never need to ask the user for file contents. After validation narrate the results. Pass the validatedRowsJson output directly to StageRosterFile without modifying it. Always confirm with the admin before triggering staging, mapping, or ingestion.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_validate2</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_validate2</masterLabel>
        <sortOrder>2</sortOrder>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <genAiPluginInstructions>
        <description>After DPE mapping is triggered, give the admin a direct link to the CRF record to review and complete the mapping. Poll using ManageRosterFieldMapping in POLL mode. Do not trigger ingestion until mappingComplete = true. When ingestion is triggered, tell the admin they can close the chat and will be notified when the job finishes. Do not mention time estimates.</description>
        <developerName>instruction_mapping3</developerName>
        <language>en_US</language>
        <masterLabel>instruction_mapping3</masterLabel>
        <sortOrder>3</sortOrder>
    </genAiPluginInstructions>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <masterLabel>Provider Roster Management</masterLabel>
    <pluginType>Topic</pluginType>
    <scope>Handle all requests related to provider roster file ingestion: processing a roster file, validating, staging, field mapping, running ingestion, and checking ingestion status or results. Triggered when the user mentions a roster file, a CRF record, or provider network data loading. The roster file is already attached to the CRF record in Salesforce — no file transfer from the user is needed.</scope>
</GenAiPlugin>
